So, if you observe any kind of armament tool that was not expected on the environment and
if you feel there is something going on, it's looked like the threat type of activity.
At that time you can block the hash of the any disc or whatever armament tools they are
using. So, by that we can delete, we can by blocking the hash the threat factor can't
able to execute that armament tools more over in the environment. So, the armament tool execution
will be get stopped and the current armament tools will be also terminated and the connections
get disconnected for a threat factor. So, they can't able to use armament tools anymore.
So, this is one of a good methods to do in our instant response while you observe the
unexpected armament tools that was giving some connections to the other connections to
the some kind of unknown IPs. As well as you can take the IP of armament tools, so which
IP it was it was connecting and you can block the IP in the EDR tool or antivirus after
so you can so you can stop the threat in the command and control section.
As well as think about that if the threat factors was in execution of the EDR tool, so think
about they have crossed many mitrotatics because mitrotatics, they have crossed the
credential axis, they have crossed the privilege escalation, different shavations, they
have performed everything and finally, they are in this section command and control and
they are they are going to do something, they are they are going to do something with an
explanation. So, this we need to really think about think about it and we need to take
appropriate response section against this. Thank you.